Guide to the Hartt School Dean's Office records ARCH114
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Hartt School Dean's Office records
1957-2010
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Hartt School. Dean's Office
ARCH114
2.13 Linear Feet (6 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
Two files, "Fuller Gifts and Bequests" and "Self-Study Report NASM Visitiation" have restricted folders. The remainder of the collection is open to all researchers.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains memos, correspondence, reports, and a small number of photographs generated during the tenures of Deans Mattran, Harris, Smith, and Morrison
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
University of Hartford -- Alumni and Alumnae; Hartt School; University of Hartford
- Acc. I Unknown, 1973-2010; I. Unknown; 1.71 Linear Feet (5 containers)
  Arrangement
  Files are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Alumni, 1996-1997, undated (Box 1)
  - Alumni and Staff Faculty, 1984-1996 (Box 1)
  - Alumni and Staff Newspaper Clippings, Circa 1990- circa 1999 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Award Dinner, 1982-2009 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Relations, 1979-1995 (Box 1)
  - Alumnus of the Year, 1985-2007 (Box 1)
  - Artists Collective, 1981-1998 (Box 1, Box Shared Oversized 1)
  - Avalon String Quartet, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Berkman, John, 1987; 1996 (Box 1)
  - Beta Fund, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1979-1985 (Box 2)
  - Brass Ring, 1981-1987 (Box 2)
  - Commencement Materials, 2000-2006 (Box 2)
  - Copeland Century, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Eppes, William, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Fuller Estate, 1997-2004 (Box 2)
  - Fuller Furniture at Hartt, 1980; 1988 (Box 2)
  - Fuller Gifts and Bequests [PARTIALLY RESTRICTED], 1962-2007 (Box 2)
  - Fuller House, 2011 (Box 2)
  - Fuller Memorial, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Fuller, Primrose, 1973-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Greater Hartford Youth Orchestra, 1987, undated (Box 2)
  - Harris, Donald, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Hartt, Julius - Letters to a Young Musician, 1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Hartt Summer Youth Music Program, 1987-1991 (Box 3)
  - Integrals Newsletter, 1957-1988 (Box 3)
  - Jazz Program, 1983, undated (Box 3)
  - Library and Museum, 1984, undated (Box 3)
  - Library Annual Reports, 1993-2002 (Box 3)
  - Miami String Quartet, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
  - Musicians Club of America (MCA), 1990, undated (Box 3)
  - Menuhin, Yehudi Visit, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
  - Mozart Bicentennial, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Paranov 95th, undated (Box 3)
  - Pellettieri Memorial, 1988 May 20 (Box 3)
  - Programs, 1999, 2008 (Box 3)
  - Project Seal, 1990-1993 (Box 3)
  - Self-Study Report NASM Visitation [PARTIALLY RESTRICTED], 1979 Sep 26 (Box 3, Box 4)
  - Schuman, William Ceremony, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Technology and Databases, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Touring and Performances, 1986-1997 (Box 4)
  - Raphael Trio, 1997-1998, undated (Box 4)
- Acc. 2011.35, 1957-2006; 0.42 Linear Feet (1 container) (Box 1)